A Guide to the Ruiz Case Office of Special Master Records, 1979-1992.
Ruiz Case Office of Special Master Records,
- Inmate pleadings and orders, 1991-1992 (Box 94-458/8 (05272755))
- Notice and proposition (Box 94-458/8 (05272755))
- Plaintiffs motions (3) (Box 94-458/8 (05272755))
- Prisoner correspondence, 1991 (Box 94-458/9 (05272416))
- TDC January-March, June-August, 1991 (Box 94-458/9 (05272416))
- OSM payment orders (Box 94-458/10 (05272369))
- OSM staff orders (Box 94-458/10 (05272369))
- OSM time and expense statements (Box 94-458/10 (05272369))
- Miscellaneous motions by non-parties (Box 94-458/10 (05272369))
- Plaintiff motions (Box 94-458/10 (05272369))
- OSM motions (Box 94-458/10 (05272369))
- Hilliard, federal custody transfer (Box 94-458/11 (05272358))
- Order of reference and amendments to order of reference Orders; November 1981 - December, January 1986 - (Box 94-458/11 (05272358))
- Plaintiff motions, 1991-1992 (Box 94-458/12 (05272325))
- Defendants motions (Box 94-458/12 (05272325))
- Defendants motions (Box 94-458/13 (05272427))
- Reports, 42nd - 58th (Box 94-458/14 (05274987))
- Non-adjudicative judicial branch, employees (4th and 10th) (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Hearing on plaintiffs' objections to amended decree (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Pre-trial order on plaintiffs' motion to modify the amended decree (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Prisoner pleadings denied (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Notes (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Lee Otis Johnson, habeas (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Aranda, Eubanks and Fuller (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Frank Smith (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Central Arkansas HSA, North Little Rock, Arkansas (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Transcripts filed (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Huh notes (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Exhibit lists, all parties (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Witness lists (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Original trial material (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Retroactivity of Ruiz (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Miscellaneous orders (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Frank Cervantes (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Contempt (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Index and froms (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Exhibit A (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Plaintiffs complaint (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- W. David Arnold, monitor to Judge Justice (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Ruiz file (Box 94-458/15 (05272700))
- Filing index guide: (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - 33rd report, draft (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - 33rd report, footnote objection (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Motion to dismiss U. S. (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - 31st report (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Ruiz (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Stipulation material (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Defendants filings, 1987 (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Gov. visit, January 1987 (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Response, prison tour, February 27, 1987 (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Ruiz vs. McCotter, H-78-987-CA, appeal notice (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Ruiz, April 1987 hearing paperwork, orders (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Ruiz hearing, April 1987 (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Ruiz, April 24th order concerning contempt MTM, 1987 (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Extensions for various reports, 1987 (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Joint motion to dismiss appeals, contempt order, April 27, 1987 (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Internal affairs (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
  - Overview appendicies, October 1986 (Box 94-458/16 (05274885))
- US District Court, Southern District of Texas, Office of the Special Master, statement of expenses, September 5, 1986 (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- Defendants' physically handicapped plan, 1986 (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- 18th quarterly compliance report, April 1987 (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- Supplemental plan for the physically handicapped defender program, March 27, 1987 (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- Texas Department of Corrections proposed construction budget, FY 1988-1989, January 6, 1987 (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- Stipulations concerning health care positions, April 1984 (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- Guadalupe Guajardo, Jr., et. al. vs. McCotter, et. al. docket, 71-H-570 (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- Ruiz evidentiary hearing, defendants exhibits, Vol. I, April 1987 (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- CA No. H-78-987, Ruiz defendants exhibit No. 3, APril 13, 1987 (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- Minutes, Ruiz/Guajardo hearing, January 13-14, 1986 (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- Plaintiff, intervenors and defendants' pleading concerning modification design of maximum security unit, March 1986 (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- Isiah Green brief files (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- File of notices and information provided to plaintiffs, June 1985 (Box 94-458/17 (05272450))
- Defendants' third memorandum in support of motion for partial summary judgement and motion to strike (Box 94-458/18 (05272449))
- Miscellaneous orders, October 1992 (Box 94-458/18 (05272449))
- Plaintiffs readings, September 1992 (Box 94-458/18 (05272449))
- Defendants pleadings (Box 94-458/18 (05272449))
- Inmate pleadings and orders, September - May 1993 (Box 94-458/18 (05272449))
- Reports of the office of the Special Master, 63rd - 68th (Box 94-458/18 (05272449))
- Kohler vs. Nathan, 1.0.64.2 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Almaguer vs. Nathan, 1.0.64.1 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- 27.6 staffing study (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- B-83-150-CA (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- TDC Qu. reports on health care (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Housing reports for May-September, 1984 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- TDC housing reports, 25.16 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Notice to TLC Lass concerning use of force stip-echo, 31.38 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Class members' objections to use of force stipulation, 31.44 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Use of force, experts reports, 31.6 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Operational audits investigation, 31.36 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Transcript on hearing on access and ad. sep. plans, 51.38 94-458/19 (05274852) Minutes,, Adseg supp. stip., disp. procedures stip. hearings held June 22, 1984 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Tousant vs. Roubin adseg, 51.49 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Class memeber objections, supp. adseg. stip. and disciplinary procedures and interim classification plan, 51.50 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Solitary confinement, memos to all counsel, 52.4 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Attorney visitation correspondence, 54.31 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Class objections, 1.7.1.50(a) (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Class member objections to access rules and adseg plans, 54.37 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Occupational health and safety plan, 60.9 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- TDC occupationalhealth and safety manual, May 1983, 60.10 (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Mentally retarded offender plan (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Defendants' discovery (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Plaintiffs discovery (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Plaintiffs discovery I (Box 94-458/19 (05274852))
- Reports of the Special Master, 60th - 62nd (Box 94-458/20 (05274900))
- Prisoner letters, January-April, 1988 (Box 94-458/20 (05274900))
- Payment orders, October 1992 (Box 94-458/20 (05274900))
- Inmate correspondence, December 1992 (Box 94-458/20 (05274900))
- 65th monitors report, 1989 (Box 94-458/20 (05274900))
- TDC, Report to the Court on Wynne use of Force Cases, 1988 (Box 94-458/20 (05274900))
- TDC Institutional Division, 1st Semi-Annual Report on State of Compliance at Eight Units of the Amended Decree, 1988 (Box 94-458/20 (05274900))
- Answered letters from Secretary of Judge Justice (Box 94-458/20 (05274900))
- Thomas vs. White, et. al. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Kohler vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Earhart vs. Ware (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Bonner vs. Staples (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Malbrue vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Smith vs. McKaskle, et. al. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Smith vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Wicker vs. Sung Lee (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Hudson vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Howard vs. Estelle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Ward vs. Warner, et. al. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Caraway vs. Brown, et. al. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Sequeiros vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Hamilton vs. Norton (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Davidson vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Rader vs. Garner, et. al. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Jones vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Moore vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Loggins aka Shebazz vs. Bailey (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Ryshard vs. Texas Board of Pardons (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Kohler vs. White (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Rader vs. White (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Riley vs. Collins (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Micheaux vs. Dr. Knox, et. al. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Montena vs. White (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Valentine vs. Ware (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Jenks vs. Summers (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Harris vs. Bennett (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Holler vs. Dr. Cox, et. al. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Watson vs. Garner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Tower vs. Clifford (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Holler vs. Redden, et. al. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Brock vs. Wade, et. al. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Linton vs. Dunham (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Lee vs. Lovelady (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Cook vs. TDC, et. al. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Rheaume, Lenny vs. Warden Garner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Ruffin vs. Beckham (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Milton vs. Officer Rogers (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Russell vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Massey vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Carter vs. Beckham (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Mikel vs. Garner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Merritt vs. McClure (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Mikel vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Loggins vs. Barrat (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Phipps vs. Summers (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Phipps vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Davis vs. Garner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Green vs. Jones (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Allen vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Frank vs. TDC (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Winn vs. Conklin (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Hernandez vs. Walker, et. al. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Everett vs. McLure (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Brownlee vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Randolph vs. Ledford (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Trent vs. McKaskle (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Butters vs. Warner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Wright vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Tate vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Sinclair vs. Simmons (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Trantham vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Duger vs. Walker (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Beck vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Bowie vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Allen, Henry (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Steinetz vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- McKelvy vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Biel vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Rice vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Ward vs. Warner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Bell vs. TDC (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Walker vs. Gonzales (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Walker vs. Lightfoot (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Rider vs. Dr. Gold, et. al. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Shead vs. Garner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Walker vs. Garner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Bruce vs. Garner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Chambers vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Rogers vs. Garner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Jenks vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Kemp vs. Garner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Lamb vs. McRory (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Walker vs. Garner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Massey vs. Garner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Sanders vs. Garner (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Corley, Robert (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Milton, W. A. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Stafford, Monte C. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Massey, Brett (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Glover vs. Collins (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Siegler vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- McShan vs. Elskes (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Vediales, Fernando (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Edgar Green (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Watson, Robert W. (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Motto, Frank John (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- James, Terry Ray (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Hernandez vs. Procunier (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Orders entered by Judge Justice for prisoner pleadings on November 30, 1983 (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Severance, transfer to Eastern District (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Severance, transfer to Southern District (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Refer to Special Master (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Sever and transfer to Eastern District, July 1984 (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Sever and transfer to Southern District, July 1984 (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Referred to Special Master, September 1984 (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Severed to Southern District, September 1984 (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Sever and transfer to the Eastern District, September 1984 (Box 94-458/21 (05272530))
- Monitoring Housing Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
- Texas Department of Corrections, quarterly compliance reports stipulating modifying crowding provisions of amended decree: (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
  - 9th, September 20, 1987 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
  - 10th, December 20, 1987 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
  - 11th, March 21, 1988 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
  - 12th, June 20, 1988 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
  - 13th, September 20, 1988 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
  - 14th, December 20, 1988 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
  - 15th, March 20, 1989 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
- Quarterly compliance reports detailing progress toward compliance with the stipulated modification of sections II.D and II.A of the amended decree: (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
  - 20th, September 1, 1987 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
  - 21st, December 19, 1987 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
  - 22nd, March 1, 1988 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
- Defendants' 1st semi-annual report on the number of security staff employed and their deployment, October 20, 1989 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
- 1st annual report on support service inmates (SSIs), January 1989 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
- 1st annual report on compliance with access to courts, counsel and public officials rules at 18 units, June 1, 1989 (Box 94-458/22 (05272405))
- Reports of the Office of Special Master, 16th, 49th-50th, 55th-59th (Box 94-458/23 (05272438))
- Receipt (Box 94-458/23 (05272438))
- Monitors reports: (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - Report of Special Master on Huntsville Unit Hospital (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - Monitor Dave Arnold's report on observations regarding compliance with stipulated modification of II.A and II.D of amended decree (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - Special masters report regarding defendants' compliance with section XII and section XIII.A of stipulated modifications (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - Report of the Special Master regarding the defendants' compliance with IV.D of amended decree granting equitable relief and Dec. J'm and section III of the consent decree (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - Appendices and 1st monitor's report of factual observations, report on II.D of amended decree granting equitable belief and declatory judgement, filed October 16, 1981 (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - Second monitor's report of factual observations to Special Master, report on sections IV.A and IV.C of amended decree granting equitable relief and declatory (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - 3rd monitor's report of factual observations to the Special Master, report V.A - V. K. of the amended decree granting equitable relief and declaratory judgement (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - 1st report of the defendants' state of compliance, overcrowding, from Special Master, November 11, 1981 (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - Texas Department of Corrections' monitoring housing report, January 4, 1985 (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - Report of Special Master on the administrative segregation plan, November 1, 1982 (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - Revision of report of Special Master on defendants' compliance with I.A.2 of amended decree granting equitable relief and declaratory judgement, review of good time credits (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - Report of Special Master on the maximum rated capacity of dorms throughout the TDC system (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - 4th monitor's report to the Special Master, report on stipulation and order modifying decree, Huntsville Hospital with appendices (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - Appendices to 6th monitor's report, Vols. I-II (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
  - 6th monitor's report and Special Master's report, IV.A. and IV.B. of the amended decree granting equitable relief and III.B of the Ad. Seg. plan, disciplinary procedures (Box 94-458/24 (05272347))
- Evelyn J. Armstrong's inmates correspondence, October 1988 - December 31, 1989 (Box 94-458/25 (05274896))
- Structural deficiencies order, overcrowding (Box 94-458/26)
- Housing reports (Box 94-458/26)
- Newspaper articles (Box 94-458/26)
- Inmate correspondence (Box 94-458/26)
- Drafts, orders (Box 94-458/26)
- Inmate mediation project, proposal (Box 94-458/26)
- MROP (Box 94-458/26)
- Minutes, rule 23, hearing Ruiz October 25, 1985 (Box 94-458/26)
- Objections to stipulation modifying crowding provisions of amended decree, 1985 (Box 94-458/26)
- Office of Special Master report, psychiatric services, February 1986 (Box 94-458/26)
- Research memos (Box 94-458/26)
- Solitary confinement, health precautions (Box 94-458/26)
- Use of force (Box 94-458/26)
- Title 37, Texas Administrative Code, Department of Corrections (Box 94-458/26)
- Case reviews, Galveston Division (Box 94-458/26)
- Ruiz update, OSM, Houston, July 17, 1986 (Box 94-458/26)
- Ruiz emergency motions (Box 94-458/26)
- Defendants' post-hearing brief in response to the show cause order of March 17, 1986 (Box 94-458/26)
- Appeal (Box 94-458/26)
- TRO (Box 94-458/26)
- Permanent instruction (Box 94-458/26)
- Stay (Box 94-458/26)
- Formally [sic] black notebook in Ruiz (Box 94-458/26)
- 5th circuit affirmance, Wolters matter, February 23, 1987 (Box 94-458/26)
- Contempt hearing exhibits (Box 94-458/26)
- Motion to find defendants' in contempt (Box 94-458/26)
- Deputy clerk instructions (Box 94-458/26)
- Minute sheets and exhibit stickers (Box 94-458/26)
- Ruiz vs. McCotter, miscellaneous and special correspondence (Box 94-458/26)
- Showcase hearing, June 2, 1986 (Box 94-458/26)
- Record of proceedings, oral hearing on defendants' motion for temporary emergency relief and plaintiffs' motion for preliminary injunction, September 15-16, 1986 (Box 94-458/26)
- Motion to find defendants' in contempt and for further relief with appendices, January 1986 (Box 94-458/26)
- Defendants' return to the show cause order of March 17, 1986 (Box 94-458/26)
- Plaintiffs' post-hearing brief on motion to find defendants' in contempt and for further relief (Box 94-458/26)
- Defendants' post-hearing brief in response to the show cause order on March 17, 1986 (Box 94-458/26)
- Exhibit summaries (Box 94-458/26)
- Ruiz vs. McCotter, H-78-987, court documents hearing (Box 94-458/26)
- Correspondence (Box 94-458/26)
- Contempt research (Box 94-458/26)
- Miscellaneous (Box 94-458/26)
- Ruiz vs. McCotter, H-78-987-CA, memorandum opinion and order (Box 94-458/26)
- Brief for plaintiffs as appellees, as court of apeals, No. 87-2077 (Box 94-458/26)
- Notebook, notes on case (Box 94-458/26)
- Defendants reports, 1989-1990: (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - Semi-annual statistical report on investigations of use of force and harassment and retaliation (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - Annual report, TDC, comprehensive health care plan (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - Special district, August 1989 (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - Medical department, August 1989 (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - Report, special district (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - Use of force reporting, review process, January-June 1990 (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - Defendants' trusty camp assessment (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - Use of force reporting, July-December 1989 (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - Defendants 1st annual report on allocation of necessities during, 1988-1989 (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - Narrative analysis of all use of force violations, July-December 1989 (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - Defendants 4th semi-annual report on stipulation modifying crowding provisions (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - 1st annual report on defendants classification system: reception and diagnostic process (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - Report on Daniel Unit health care services (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
  - 1st annual report on defendants classification system: Appendix, E-K (Box 94-458/27 (05272733))
- Severed to Southern District, July 1985 (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Sent to Special Master, July 1985 (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Sent to Special Master, August 1985 (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Sever and transfer to Eastern District, August 1985 (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Sever and transfer to Southern District (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- July 21, 1981 (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Sever and transfer to Eastern District (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Sent to Special Master, September 1985 (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Refer to Special Master, October 1985 (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Refer to Special Master, November 1985 (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Refer to Special Master, December 1985 (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Report to the Special Master (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Special masters report, December 1984 (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- 26th monitors report (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- 33rd masters report, September 1986 (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Revised health care plan, Vols. I-III (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- 25th monitors reort, Vols. I-II (Box 94-458/28 (05274965))
- Civil action, No. H-78-987 (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
- Loose papers (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
- Civil action No. H-78-987-CA: (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
  - Modifying decree (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
  - Temporary restraining order (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
  - Order (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
- US Court of Appeals (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
- Civil action No. H-78-987, 5th application for enforcement of the amended order of reference of July 24, 1981 (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
- Civil action No. H-78-987, 3rd application for enforcement of the amended order of reference of July 24, 1981 (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
- Mandamus (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
- Motion of temporary restraining order (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
- Employee list, Texas DOC (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
- Final pre-trail order on plaintiffs motion to modify decree (Box 94-458/29 (05268135))
- Fourth annual compliance report, February 3, 1989 (Box 94-458/30 (05274659))
- Stipulation modifying crowding provisions of amended decree, January 14, 1986 (Box 94-458/30 (05274659))
- First annual compliance report: Stipulation modifying crowding compliance report on staffing Vol. I II, January 20, 1986 (Box 94-458/30 (05274659))
- Third annual compliance report: Stipulation modifying crowding compliance report on staffing Vol. I II, February 1, 1986 (Box 94-458/30 (05274659))
- Appendices to third annual report (Box 94-458/30 (05274659))
- Defendants third semi-annual report on section III of the stipulation modifying crowding provisions of the amended decrees, Vols. I II, August 1, 1989 (Box 94-458/30 (05274659))
- Defendants second semi-annual report on section III of the stipulation modifying crowding provisions of the amended decrees, Vols. I II, February 3, 1989 (Box 94-458/30 (05274659))